nexteve.com 2013-08-02

# Privacy

NextEve.com (the Site) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others.

Order:

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information ( name and shipping address) and financial information ( credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. From time to time, we may e-mail you with new offers.

Cookies:

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.

Log Files:

Currently we're NOT logging any IP address of our visitors. However we reserve to use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
Unsolicited Emails   
Customer will not receive any continual email solicitation from the Site, unless the customer consents to the solicitation at checkout/registration, or thorough a double opt-in process. And, if the customer does consent to receive email from the company, the company agrees to have a simple unsubscribe option available, along with unsubscribe instructions in every email.

Sharing:

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We do NOT store customers' Credit Card information locally.  
These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

Security:

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing’.  
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.  
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can contact us.

Notification of Changes:  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
